{
    "0": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    20%",
            "B.    30%",
            "C.    50%",
            "D.    70%"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "1) There are 40 children in class. 16 of them are girls. How many percent more boys than girls are there?"
    },
    "1": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : A.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    $2600",
            "B.    $2450",
            "C.    $2200",
            "D.    $2050"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "2) Every month Rani gives 65% of her salary to her mother. She spends 15% of her salary and saves the remainder. She saves $130 more than what she spends. What is her monthly salary?"
    },
    "2": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : A.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    50",
            "B.    60",
            "C.    70",
            "D.    80"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "3) The ratio of the number of apples in Box A to the number of apples in Box B is 3:2. All the apples in Box B are green. The ratio of the number of green apples to the number of red apples in Box A is 4:5. There are 20 more green apples in Box B than in Box A. How many red apples are there?"
    },
    "3": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : B.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    320",
            "B.    240",
            "C.    400",
            "D.    160"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "4) A, B and C shared some stickers in the ratio of 3:1:4. After C gave 40% of her stickers to A and B, A had 90 more stickers than C and the number of B's stickers increased by 70%. How many stickers did C have at first?"
    },
    "4": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : D.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    1:3",
            "B.    3:1",
            "C.    1:2",
            "D.    2:1"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "5) Box A and Box B contained some books in the ratio 5 : 2. There were 54 more books in Box A than in Box B. If 6 books were transferred from Box A to Box B, what would be the new ratio of the number of books in Box A to that in Box B?"
    },
    "5": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    186",
            "B.    248",
            "C.    184",
            "D.    176"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "6) Raja had as much money as Rani. After Raja spent $132 and Rani spent $54, the amount of money they had left was in the ratio 2:5. Find the amount of money each of them had at first."
    },
    "6": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : A.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    285",
            "B.    190",
            "C.    320",
            "D.    256"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "7) In a club, the ratio of the number of adults to the number of children is 12 :7. The ratio of the number of boys to the number of girls is 3 : 2. If there are 42 girls, how many members are there altogether?"
    },
    "7": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : C.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    60",
            "B.    74",
            "C.    96",
            "D.    108"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "8) Find the missing number in the following series:\n6    120    12    108    24    ?    48    84"
    },
    "8": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : A.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    36",
            "B.    48",
            "C.    24",
            "D.    60"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "9) Raja and Rani collected some phone cards in the ratio 3 : 2. When Raja gave away 42 of his phone cards, the ratio of the number of Raja`s phone cards to Rani`s phone cards became 1 : 3. How many phone cards did Rani collect?"
    },
    "9": {
        "answer": "Answer / Explanation :\n\nAnswer : D.",
        "option_texts": [
            "A.    358",
            "B.    232",
            "C.    76",
            "D.    147"
        ],
        "question_img_src": "https://raffles.guru/image/blank.gif",
        "question_text": "10) Rani and Raja collected some stamps in the ratio 1 : 2. When Rani received 35 stamps from Raja, the ratio of the number of Rani`s stamps to Raja`s stamps became 4 : 3. How many stamps did they have altogether?"
    }
}